Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Objects and Artifacts, 1914-1992
  - Subseries A: General Objects and Artifacts
    - Stamp, undated; cuid27981 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0259)
      Materials: wood, rubber
      Dimensions: 0.5 x 1.85 x 2.5 inches
    - Stamp Kit, undated; cuid27982 (Box 123, Object 092.2.0260)
      Description: Kit consists of upper and lower case letters, numbers, and various symbols; upper and lower case letters, numbers, and various symbols; ruler, metal guide; in green box; set appears to be complete
      Maker: label on side of box cover reads "Columbia, sign and chart printers, 02"
      Materials: wood, rubber, ink
    - Camera, undated; cuid27983 (Box 182, Object 092.2.0261)
      Description: Konica autoreflex A 1000 manual camera in leather case
      Maker: Konica--on front of camera and lens cap
      Where Made: Japan--stamped on back right of leather case
      Materials: metal, plastic, glass, leather
      Dimensions: 4.5 x 6 x 4 inches
    - Camera, undated; cuid27984 (Box 182, Object 092.2.0262)
      Description: Konica manual camera in leather case, lens cap missing
      Maker: Konica--on front of camera and case
      Where Made: Japan "Made in Japan" stamped on back right of case
      Materials: Metal, plastic, glass, leather
      Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5 x 3.25 inches
    - Keychain, undated; cuid27985 (Box 180, Object 092.2.0263)
      Description: Keychain with miniature toy camera attached, black and gold
      Materials: plastic, metal
      Dimensions: 1.75 x 2.25 x 1.65 inches
    - Box of splicing tape (super 8 sound), undated; cuid27986 (Box 195, Object 092.2.0264)
      Description: Box containing six individual packets of splicing tape for super 8 film, each packet contains 50 pieces, instructions in German.
      Maker: Wurker--printed on box and packets
      Where Made: "Made in Germany" printed on box and packets
      Materials: splicing tape, cardboard
      Dimensions: 7.25 x 2.65 x 1 inches
    - Film Splicer, undated; cuid27987 (Box 195, Object 092.2.0265)
      Description: Film splicer for super 8 sound film, in original box
      Maker: Wurker--stamped on splicer, printed on box
      Where Made: "Made in Germany" stamped on bottom of splicer, printed on box
      Materials: Metal, plastic, cardboard
      Dimensions: 2.25 x 3.5 x 5.15 inches
    - Focus enlarger, undated; cuid27988 (Box 195, Folder 092.2.0266)
      Description: Focus enlarger
      Maker: Label on bottom states "Bestwell optical Inst Co."
      Where Made: Label on bottom states "209 Beverly Road, Bklyn. 18, NY"
      Materials: Metal, glass, paint
      Dimensions: 6.35 x 2.5 x 6.5 inches
    - Toy Spider, undated; cuid27989 (Box 161, Folder 092.2.0267)
      Description: Hand-made toy depicting spider, with string pull and roller underneath, black with green dots
      Materials: wood, leather, paint, string, rubber, rubber bands
      Dimensions: 1.15 x 4.5 x 3.65 inches
    - Kachina, undated; cuid27990 (Box 126, Folder 092.2.0268)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll featuring bull horns, protruding eyes, feathers on crown of head and tail. Multi-colored.
      Materials: wood, feathers, thread, paint
      Dimensions: 9 x 3.65 x 2 inches
    - Kachina, undated; cuid27991 (Box 158, Folder 092.2.0269)
      Description: Hand-carved wood machine doll featuring feather headdress, bull horns, protruding eyes, leather skirt, with painted snake, beard, moccasins, and leopard fur cape. Multi-colored.
      Materials: wood, feathers, paper, paint, fur, leather, yarn
      Dimensions: 9 x 4.5 x 3.75 inches
    - Kachina, undated; cuid27992 (Box 126, Folder 092.2.0270)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll featuring geometric headdress with feathers, geometric designs, protruding mouth/nose. Multi-colored.Note: object not freestanding
      Materials: wood, feathers, paint
      Dimensions: 11 x 2.5 x 2.25 inches
    - Kachina, undated; cuid27993 (Box 127, Folder 092.2.0271)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll featuring protruding mouth, butterfly in back of head; black & white & terracotta.
      Maker: Label bottom of right foot reads "Nayaiataka"
      Materials: wood, paint, feather, string
      Dimensions: 5.25 x 3.15 x 2 inches
    - Kachina, undated; cuid27994 (Box 162, Folder 092.2.0272)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll featuring stick headdress, pronounced yoke or collar on neck, tail in back. Multi-colored.
      Dimensions: 7.5 x 2.25 x 2.25 inches
    - Kachina/Squash-man figure, undated; cuid27995 (Box 162, Folder 092.2.0273)
      Description: Hand-carved wood Kachina doll with human male body and squash---shaped head; painted green and black stripes, yellow disc on back of head, yellow maracas in hands, cloth loincloth attached, glued to wood base.
      Maker: Bottom of base reads "Squash by Andrea Naha"
      Materials: wood, paint, cloth, leather, yarn, glue
      Dimensions: 8.5 x 4.25 x 4 inches
    - Kachina/Figurine, undated; cuid27996 (Box 126, Folder 092.2.0274)
      Description: Kachina-esque figurine of male body with head covered by hood with geometric symbols, fur trim around neck, loincloth with geometric designs, yarn tied around ankles--sticks held in each hand. Back loincloth broken off.
      Maker: Markings on bottom of feet illegible
      Materials: clay, paint, fur, yarn, wood
      Dimensions: 6.75 x 5.25 x 2 inches
    - Miniature Kachina, undated; cuid27997 (Box 127, Folder 092.2.0275)
      Description: Carved wood Kachina dancing figure with Mohawk, loincloth, tail, moccasins. Body painted half yellow, half green.
      Materials: wood, paint, fur glue
      Dimensions: 5.25 x 2.75 x 2.25 inches
    - Figurine, undated; cuid27998 (Box 130, Folder 092.2.0276)
      Description: Figurine of mythological character or god, featuring plumed headdress, wings, and leopard spots; probably Latin-American
      Dimensions: 7 x 4.25 x 3.25 inches
    - Figurine, undated; cuid27999 (Box 158, Folder 092.2.0277)
      Description: Hand-carved wood figure, unfinished, unpainted, featuring long hair and bangs.
      Dimensions: 6.25 x 3.75 x 2 inches
    - Miniature figurine, undated; cuid28000 (Box 181, Folder 092.2.0278)
      Description: Miniature of Native American dancer wearing feathered headdress, mask, skirt and feather cuffs on arms. Multi-colored.
      Dimensions: 2.5 x 2.5 x 1 inches
    - Miniature Mask, undated; cuid28001 (Box 127, Folder 092.2.0279)
      Description: Mask depicting jaguar face with open mouth and teeth and straw plumes projecting from face
      Maker: markings on back illegible
      Materials: wood, paint, straw
      Dimensions: 2.75 x 4.75 x 1.5 inches
    - Palm leaf manuscript--engraved, undated; cuid28002 (Box 158, Folder 092.2.0280)
      Description: Palm leaf manuscript with an inscription on one side and elaborately decorated on the other. Script appears to be derived from Sanskrit and could potentially be Burmese, Tibetan, etc. To close the manuscript, a string is wound around the manuscript and held in place with what appears to be a Chinese coin.
      Maker: none identifiable
      Materials: wood, paint, metal coin, string
      Dimensions: 9.75 x 1.5 x 0.75 inches
    - Double-headed figurine, undated; 092.2.0281; 1 item one figurine (Box 193, Object 092.2.0281)
      Description: Siamese-twin figurine featuring two heads on either end of torso, double faces on each head, black and white stripes on body and illegible inscription on both sides of torso. Both heads have glass tops revealing bark or hair inside.
      Materials: plaster, paint, glass, hair, wire, bark or bone, string
      Dimensions: 10 x 8.5 x 1.5 inches
      Figurines.; Sculpture (visual works)
    - Paperweight-globe, undated; cuid28003 (Box 181, Object 092.2.0282)
      Description: Multi-colored globe encase in clear Lucite cube
      Materials: Lucite, metal
      Dimensions: 2 x 2 x 2 inches
    - Globe, undated; cuid28004 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0283)
      Description: Hollow metal globe, multi-colored, probably meant to come apart as container. Items duplicate of 092.2.0284 and 092.2.0285
      Dimensions: 1.65 inches
    - Globe, undated; cuid28005 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0284)
      Description: Hollow metal globe, multi-colored, probably meant to come apart as a container; item is duplicate of 092.2.0283 and 092.2.0258
    - Globe, undated; cuid28006 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0285)
      Description: Hollow metal globe, multi-colored, opens up as a container. Item is duplicate of 092.2.0283 and 092.2.0284
    - Globe, undated; cuid28007 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0286)
      Description: Miniature globe opens up a into container. Multi-colored. Item is duplicate of 092.2.0287-092.2.0290
      Dimensions: 1 inches
    - Globe, undated; cuid28008 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0287)
      Description: Miniature globe opens up as container; multi-colored. Item is duplicate of 092.2.0286-092.2.0290
    - Globe, undated; cuid28009 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0288)
    - Globe, undated; cuid28606 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0289)
    - Globe, undated; cuid28010 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0290)
    - Globe, undated; cuid28011 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0291)
      Description: Globe on stand which depicts signs of the zodiac, the seasons and months of the year. Seam along circumference of globe forms a lip. Multi-colored
      Maker: "off the coast of Chile, printed ""Ohio Art Co., Bryan Ohio""n.d."
      Where Made: Ohio USA--printed on globe (near Chile)
      Dimensions: 8.75 x 6 x 6inches
    - Globes, undated; cuid28012 (Box 187, Object 092.2.0292)
      Description: Globe on stand with paint removed to reveal tin surface, with wooden figure (broken) and cardboard cylinder shell of firework attached with yellow wire
      Maker: none, but possible David Wojnarowicz
      Materials: tin, paint, wood, cardboard, wire
      Dimensions: 8.75 x 9 x 9inches
    - Yo-Yo toy, undated; cuid28013 (Box 181, Object 092.2.0293)
      Description: Yo-yo sphere with map of continents. Multi-colored
      Maker: stamped "yos" along center (near South America)
      Materials: plastic, paint, string
      Dimensions: 2.25 x x inches
    - Coin-bank globe, undated; cuid28014 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0294)
      Description: Coin bank in shape of globe featuring "old-fashioned" map of world; coin slot on top
      Dimensions: 4.75 x 4 x 4inches
    - Globe puzzle--in box, undated; cuid28015 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0295)
      Description: Globe with moving parts in manner of a "Rubik's cube" game; in original box
      Where Made: bottom of box stamped 'Logomb in Hungary"
      Dimensions: 3.5 x 3.5 x 3.5inches
    - Globe in box, undated; cuid28016 (Box 125, Object 092.2.0296)
      Description: Globe in cardboard box, original information booklet indicates a magnifying glass was originally included but is now missing, multi-colored globe. Red box
      Maker: "Replogle" printed on box and on globe (equator)
      Materials: cardboard, ink
      Dimensions: 6 x 4.75 x 5inches
    - Globe, undated; cuid28017 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0297)
      Description: World Globe, multi-colored
      Dimensions: 2.65 x 0 x 0inches
    - Globe, metal, paint; cuid28018 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0298)
      Description: Large globe, place names in French, multi-colored
      Maker: "Cartes Taride" printed on bottom
      Materials: "Fabrique en France" printed on bottom
    - Globe, undated; cuid28019 (Box 178, Object 092.2.0299)
      Description: Large globe with circular openings on top and bottom (North and South); place names in French, multi-colored
      Dimensions: 7.75 inches
    - Globe/Ball, undated; cuid28020 (Box 181, Object 092.2.0300)
      Description: Ball with world map printed encase in clear ball filled with water/liquid
      Where Made: "Taiwan" stamped on outer ball
      Materials: plastic, water
      Dimensions: 1.5 inches
    - Globe bank, cuid28021 (Item 092.2.0247, Object 092.2.0301)
      Description: Coin bank in shape of globe
      Materials:
    - Hologram, 1972 printed on back; cuid28022 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0302)
      Description: Large hologram image of head & torso of Jesus on cross, wearing crown of thorns, dripping blood. Eyes open and close.
      Maker: "edmur metal products, Inc" printed on back
      Where Made: Japan--printed on back
      Materials: plastic, photograph, cardboard, commercially produced
      Dimensions: 16 x 12 x inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28023 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0303)
      Description: 3 dimensional image of cows in front of barn; two strips of magnet on back
      Maker: none--"V.G.A" written on back
      Materials: Plastic, photograph, cardboard, Commercially produced.
      Dimensions: 12 x 16 x inches
    - Hologram, undated; cuid28024 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0304)
      Description: Hologram of Christ wearing crown of thorns. Eyes open and close. Framed. Titled "Miracle Eyes" Crucifixion on back.
      Where Made: back bottom right printed "Printed in Japan"
      Materials: plastic, photographic image, cardboard, plastic frame, commercially produced
      Dimensions: 11.5 x 9.35 x 1 inches
    - 3-D Image of Woman, undated; cuid28025 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0305)
      Description: 3-D Image of young woman amidst orchids wearing strapless dress. Multi-colored, blue background. Framed
      Maker: label on back states "W.C. Jones Publishing Co."
      Where Made: label on back states "Printed in Japan"
      Dimensions: 13.5 x 10.65 x 0.25 inches
    - 3-D Image-Horse, undated; cuid28026 (Box 175, Object 092.2.0306)
      Description: 3D image of brown horse running at a sunset.
      Materials: plastic, photographic image, cardboard, commercially produced
      Dimensions: 13.5 x 10.5 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28027 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0307)
      Description: 3-D Image depicts eagle perched on mountain top, wings open. Item identical to 092.2.0308
      Maker: Back bottom right corner printed c. Wonder c. Tokyo
      Where Made: back bottom right corner printed "made in Japan"
      Dimensions: 13 x 10.35 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28028 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0308)
      Description: 3-D image depicts eagle perched on mountain top wings open. Item identical to 092.2.0307
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28029 (Box 175, Object 030.2.0309)
      Description: 3-D image depicting horses running in Southwestern American desert. Item same as 092.2.0310
      Maker: Back bottom right corner printed "c. Wonder c. Tokyo"
      Dimensions: 10.35 x 13 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28030 (Box 175, Object 092.2.0310)
      Description: 3-D image depicting horses running in Southwestern American desert. Item same as 092.2.0309
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28031 (Box 165, Object 092.2.0311)
      Description: 3-D image depicting crucifixion of Jesus Christ with mourners. In plastic wrap.
      Where Made: sticker on back states "Made in Taiwan R.O.C."
      Dimensions: 13.5 x 10.25 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28032 (Box 175, Object 092.2.0312)
      Description: 3-D Image of a fawn lying down
      Dimensions: 10.5 x 13 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28033 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0313)
      Description: 3-D Image of two 18th century war ships. Item same as 092.2.0320
      Where Made: back top left printed "Made in Taiwan"
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28034 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0314)
      Description: 3-D Image of 18th century war ship with sails, in plastic sleeve
      Where Made: back bottom right printed "Made in Taiwan"
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28035 (Box 165, Object 092.2.0315)
      Description: 3-D image of the Last Supper.
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28036 (Box 165, Object 092.2.0316)
      Description: 3-D image of Jesus kneeling and looking up to Heaven. In plastic sleeve.
      Dimensions: 13 x 10.5 inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28037 (Box 175, Object 092.2.0317)
      Description: 3-D image of ducks on lake and flying in air. Price sticker of $4.99 on bottom left. Tape and metal hanging hook on back.
      Dimensions: inches
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28038 (Box 165, Object 092.2.0318)
      Description: 3-D image of parrots perched on tree branch. Item same as 092.2.0319
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28039 (Box 165, Object 092.2.0319)
      Description: 3-D image of parrots perched on tree branch. Item same as 092.2.0318
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28040 (Box 129, Object 092.2.0320)
      Description: 3-D image of two 18th century war ships. Item same as 092.2.0313
      Where Made: Back top left printed "Made in Taiwan"
    - 3-D Image, undated; cuid28041 (Box 175, Object 092.2.0321)
      Description: 3-D image of Horse with trees with red and yellow leaves
      Where Made: Back bottom right printed "Made in Japan"
    - Hologram, undated; cuid28042 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0322)
      Description: Hologram images of sperm. Top and bottom read "COBA/SELECT SIRESS, INC."
      Maker: "COBA/SELECT SIRESS, INC."
      Materials: plastic, image, cardboard
      Dimensions: 3.15 x 9.5 inches
    - Hologram pin, undated; cuid28043 (Box 167, Folder 092.2.0323)
      Description: Circular pin with hologram image of Elvis Presley singing
      Maker: Back printed "Vari-vue"
      Where Made: Back printed "Mt. Vernon, NY, USA
      Materials: plastic, image, metal.
      Dimensions: 3 inches
    - Hologram, undated; cuid28044 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0324)
      Description: Hologram of planet exploding, red background
      Dimensions: 4.75 x 3.5 inches
    - Hologram, undated; cuid28045 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0325)
      Description: Hologram of green arrows
      Where Made: back printed "Mount Vernon, NY, Ptd. USA
      Materials: Plastic, photographic image, cardboard
      Dimensions: 2.15 x 1.65 inches
    - Hologram, undated; cuid28046 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0326)
      Description: Promotional hologram strip depicting an eagle in flight and reading "Special Effects" and "Eagle, The Thermal Mug People"
      Maker: front left printed "Insert made by Vari-vue ASI #7807"
      Materials: plastic, illustration, cardboard
      Dimensions: 3.25 x 10.5 inches
    - Hologram, undated; cuid28047 (Box 167, Object 092.2.0327)
      Description: Hologram images depicting dance moves for dances "jerk" and "frug"
      Maker: back reads "Vari-vue"
      Where Made: back reads "Mount Vernon, NY. Made in USA"
      Materials: plastic, illustrated image, cardboard
      Dimensions: 1.35 x 3.85 inches
    - Framed portrait, undated; cuid28048 (Box 127, Object 092.2.0328)
      Description: Pen and ink multi-colored portrait of man, possibly D. Wojnarowicz, with skull on shirt
      Maker: none, possibly James Romberger
      Materials: paper, inks, glue; frame--wood, paint glass
      Dimensions: 7 x 5 inches
    - Framed Picture, 1986; cuid28049 (Box 131, Object 092.2.0329)
      Description: Photographic image of two skeletons in gold frame. Image is post card invitation--back reads "Ulay & Marina Abramovic, Vendredi 18 aprile 1986, ore 19" and "museo d'artecontomporanea"
      Maker: see above description
      Materials: cardboard, plastic
    - Plaque, undated; cuid28050 (Box 109, Folder 092.2.0340)
      Description: Plaque of a human eye, left side, brown iris
      Maker: Label on back reads "Angelical Collection" with symbol of an angel
      Where Made: label on back reads "Made in Spain"
      Materials: ceramic, glaze, glass
      Dimensions: 3.75 x 5.25 x 0.75 inches
    - Plaque, undated.; cuid28051 (Box 127, Object 092.2.0341)
      Description: Plaque with photographic image of male mouth sewn shut with thread
      Materials: wood, paint, photograph
      Dimensions: 3 x 3 x 0.25 inches
    - Framed artwork "I Don't Like Broccoli", undated; cuid28052 (Box 159, Object 092.2.0342)
      Description: Framed cover of Time magazine with cracked and distressed glass and phrase "I Don't like Broccoli" painted over surface.
      Materials: paper, cardboard, paint, plastic; Frame-wood, paint, nails
      Dimensions: 10.75 x 8.75 x 0.5 inches
    - Road sign--Mine Field (Terrain Mine), undated; cuid28053 (Box 138, Object 092.2.0343)
      Description: Metal road sign with skull and crossbones on red background. Bottom reads "Terrain Mine." Corner holes for screws. Bottom right screw intact. Others missing.
      Materials: metal, ink
      Dimensions: 11.75 x 15.75 x 1.5 inches
    - Toy Gun (Buck Rogers), undated; cuid28054 (Box 164, Object 092.2.0344)
      Description: Stylized tow gun with engraving on chamber--reads "Buck Rogers, 25th Century"
      Maker: Near handle engraved "Daisy Manufacturing, Co., Plymouth, Mich. USA"
      Where Made: n.p., possibly Plymouth Michigan
      Dimensions: 5.5 x 7 x 1.65 inches
    - Toy Gun, undated possibly 1914; cuid28055 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0345)
      Description: Old-fashioned style revolver toy gun, back below barrel stamped "Invincible"
      Maker: Front-side, under chamber stamped "Kilgore, Patd Dec 14" and near trigger stamped with symbol K
      Where Made: Front-side, under chamber, stamped "Made in USA"
      Materials: Metal
      Dimensions: 3.75 x 5.5 x 0.75 inches
    - Toy Gun, undated; cuid28056 (Box 164, Object 092.2.0346)
      Description: Revolver with extra long barrel; black
      Dimensions: 4.75 x 9 x 1.65 inches
    - Toy Gun, undated; cuid28057 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0347)
      Description: Old-fashioned (19th C) style revolver, under chamber reads ?"Big B-ll" "u" is missing
      Maker: back near trigger stamped with symbol K. Mark of Kilgore
      Dimensions: 3.5 x 5 x 0.75 inches
    - Toy Gun, undated; cuid28058 (Box 164, Object 092.2.0348)
      Description: Revolver with long barrel; "Military Model .45" Printed on barrel, WWI style soldier figure printed don chamber; blue, orange, yellow, brown
      Dimensions: 4 x 8 x 1.25 inches
    - Toy Gun, 1967-05; cuid28059 (Box 180, Object 092.2.0349)
      Description: Revolver, moving chamber, short barrel, front of barrel stamped "CAL .33 special." Cap gun.
      Maker: Stamped on Chamber--symbol of shield with crown above, initials "G.T."
      Where Made: Front of chamber stamped "Made in Italy"
      Dimensions: 4.25 x 5.75 x 1.5 inches
    - Toy Gun, undated; cuid28060 (Box 180, Object 092.2.0350)
      Description: Automatic pistol, styled realistically; black and brown
      Maker: Handle stamped "IDEAL" and barrel stamped "IDEAL-MODEL PK/90"
      Where Made: front of barrel stamped "Made in Germany"
      Dimensions: 4 x 6.25 x 1 inches
    - Toy Gun, undated; cuid28061 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0351)
      Description: Miniature automatic pistol
      Materials: cast metal
      Dimensions: 3 x 4.5 x 0.5 inches
    - Toy Gun, undated; cuid28062 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0352)
      Description: Automatic pistol, back of barrel stamped "Presto"
      Maker: "Presto"
    - Toy Gun, undated; cuid28063 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0353)
      Description: Miniature cap gun with double barrel.
      Where Made: Trigger stamped "JAPAN"
      Dimensions: 2.5 x 3.5 x 0.75 inches
    - Lighter (Gun Shape), undated; cuid28064 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0354)
      Description: "Shoot-a Lite" Safety gas liter--printed on side of gun shaped lighter
      Maker: "Shoot-A-Lite" stamped on handle
      Where Made: "Made in USA" stamped on handle
      Dimensions: 3.25 x 6 x 0.35 inches
    - Scissors, undated; cuid28065 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0355)
      Description: Long metal scissors with square finger holes.
      Maker: Stamped at joint--"Geller & Co."
      Where Made: stamped at joint--"Germany"
      Dimensions: 9.25 x 3 x 0.25 inches
    - Knife, undated; cuid28066 (Box 128, Object 092.2.0356)
      Description: Dagger with five circles cut out of handle; blade is serrated towards bottom; black
      Dimensions: 7.65 x 1.15 x 0.25 inches